M. L. Parrish Collection of Victorian Novelists, 1806-1958 (bulk 1830s-1930s ): Finding Aid C0171
Manuscripts Division
- Series 3: Author Portraits, 1780-1995; 3 boxes; 18 items
  - Du Maurier, George Louis Palmella Busson, 1834-1896; 1 box
    - Includes one etching based on a portrait sketch by Du Maurier; and various portraits relating to Trilby, Du Maurier's 1894 novel that was dramatized for the London stage in 1895 (see Box 100 for his pencil study for Trilby ), undated; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Eliot, George, pseud. (Marian Cross, née Evans), 1819-1880; 1 box
    - Includes two cabinet cards and several other portraits, undated; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5a)
  - Faithfull, Emily, 1835-1895; 1 box
    - Includes one portrait from a collection titled "Some Women's Shadows" and several other portraits with articles in various publications, 1864-1895, undated; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5b)
  - Furniss, Harry, 1854-1925; 1 box
    - Photograph of Furniss inscribed to Major Pond, signed by Furniss, undated; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5c)
  - Gaskell, Elizabeth Cleghorn (Stevenson), 1810-1865; 1 box
    - One photograph, one pen-and-ink drawing, copies of one portrait, undated; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 6)
      Includes "St. Valentine's Day. 1864": a mock-valentine sent to Gaskell, apparently by her Publisher George Smith, of Smith, Elder & Co. A pen-and-ink drawing, approx. 10" square, with central scene surrounded by 19 additional scenes, and a bottom panel of eight lines of rhymed text pleading for more copy. The central picture shows Elizabeth Gaskell in a farmyard, bearing a milkmaid's yoke and looking at a cow, whilst (almost surreptitiously) handing a manuscript to a kneeling George Smith. This is surrounded by the9 smaller images, presumably illustrating Cousin Phillis, rather like a medieval stained-glass window or a panel of a saint's life. In fact Gaskell, who is said to have much preferred dealing with Smith rather than the editor, did contribute further to the Cornhill: she was already planning her next – and, as it turned out, final – novel, Wives and Daughters, which began to appear in the August number of the same year.
  - Hardy, Thomas, 1840-1928; 1 box
    - Includes several portraits of Hardy and photos of his birthplace and Max Gate homes (see oversize Box 100, Folder 15 for one additional photo portrait), undated; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Hughes, Thomas, 1822-1896; 1 box
    - Includes five carte-de-visite and other photos; plus several other portraits (see Box 104 for two additional caricature portraits of Hughes), undated; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Kingsley, Charles, 1819-1875; 1 box
    - Two cabinet and fourteen carte-de-visite photo cards and many other photos; plus several other portraits (see Box 100 for one additional photo portrait)*, undated; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Lever, Charles James, 1806-1872; 1 box
    - One carte-de-visite photograph and two other portraits, undated; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Lytton, Edward George Earle Lytton Bulwer-Lytton, 1st Baron, 1803-1877; 1 box
    - Includes seven carte-de-visite photographs and seven other photos; one group portrait of Lord Bulwer Lytton, Lord Macauley, T. Carlyle, Makepeace Thackeray, Charles Dickens, Geo. Mac-Donald, A. J. Froude, Wilkie Collins, and Anthony Trollope; and numerous other portraits of Lytton, undated; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Maxwell, Mary Elizabeth (Braddon), 1837-1915; 1 box
    - Two carte-de-visite photographs, two photo postcards, and two other photos, undated; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Meredith, George, 1828-1909; 1 box
    - Three portraits, including one mounted on cardboard, undated; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Reade, Charles, 1814-1884; 1 box
    - Includes a news clipping containing a "Letter of Charles Reade to his brother in India" and the wording of the inscription on Reade's tombstone; photograph and negative of a portrait in oil bequeathed by Reade to Harper & Brothers; two cabinet cards and two other photos of Reade; and numerous other portraits (see Box 100, Folder 18 for one caricature portrait), undated; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Stevenson, Robert Louis, 1850-1894; 1 box
    - Includes photograph and negative of the bronze plaque by Augustus Saint-Gaudens and a negative of the Stevenson portrait by Count Girolamo Nerli; four carte-de-visite photographs; commemorative postage stamps issued by Western Samoa (site of Stevenson's Vaillima residence and tomb); and several other portraits., undated; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace, 1811-1863; 1 box
    - Includes four carte-de-visite photos; photos of Marble Bust of Thackeray when a Boy; E. S. Wells Kerr/Photographs to illustrate Letters of Anne Thackeray Ritchie, London, John Murray, 1924; and numerous other portraits, undated; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Trollope, Anthony, 1815-1882; 1 box
    - One cabinet photo and ten carte-de-visite photo cards and several other photos; six negatives of photo portraits; and numerous other portraits (see Box 100, Folder 19 for one caricature portrait), undated; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Trollope, Frances (Milton), 1780-1863; 1 box
    - Nine copies of one portrait, undated; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Wood, Ellen (Price), 1814-1887; 1 box
    - Two copies of an original London theatre program of East Lynne and a few portraits, undated; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Yonge, Charlotte Mary, 1823-1901; 1 box
    - Two cabinet photo cards and several other photographs, undated; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Additional Author Portraits located in the Taylor Room, 1811-1995; 16 items
    - Dickens, Charles, 1812-1870; 4 items
      - Charcoal portrait by Samuel Laurence (1812-1884), 28.5 x 22.75 in., framed, [1860?], undated; 1 item
      - Lithographed portrait in colors, after E. Goodwyn Lewis, signed by Dickens on the mount, 23 x 18 inches, 1869; 1 item
    - Hardy, Thomas, 1840-1928; 8 items
      - Signed charcoal portrait by Reginald Grenville Eves (1876-1941), 25 x 21 in., framed, 1923; 1 item
      - Signed oil portrait by Reginald Grenville Eves (1876-1941), 22.5 x 19 in, undated; 1 item
      - Thackeray, William Makepeace, 1811-1863; 1 item
      - Plaster statuette by Sir Joseph Edgar Boehm (1834-1890), Bucciani & Co.(London), 20.5 in, 1860; 1 item
    - Trollope, Anthony, 1815-1882; 4 items
      - Signed portrait by Samuel Laurence (1812-1884), in charcoal, pencil, and chalk, 33.5 x 27 in. framed, 1864; 1 item
      - Statuette by Gertrude Fass (1909- ), in bronze, 16.5" high, on black micarta base, from the workshop of Domenico Ranieri (New York) -- #4 of 250 castings worldwide, 1995; 1 item
  - Oversize Item in the University Librarian's Office, 1850-1894; 2 items
    - Stevenson, Robert Louis, 1850-1894; 2 items
      - Signed bronze circular medallion by Augustus Saint-Gaudens (1848-1907) of Stevenson reading in bed, propped by pillows and holding a cigarette, 34.5 in. diameter, in octagonal frame, 1887; 1 item
- Series 4: Parrish Correspondence, 1913-1944; 39 boxes; 2 items
  Consists of Parrish's correspondence with book collectors and dealers, family members of the Victorian novelists he collected, scholars, etc., filed alphabetically by correspondent and/or subject.
  Arranged alphabetically by correspondent.
  - A (General), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Academy of Natural Sciences, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Adams, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Adler, Elmer, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Admiralty Island, undated; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Alaska, undated; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Aldus, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Allen, J. A., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - American Autograph Shop, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - American Art Assoc. - Anderson Galleries, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - American Book Company, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Amory, Mrs. Harcourt, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Antiquarian Book Company, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Argosy Book Stores, Inc, 1930-1937; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Argosy Book Stores, 1938-1944; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Argus Book Shop, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Arlington Book Shop, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Athenaeum of Philadelphia, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Ba - Bm (General), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Bo - Bz (General), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Backus, Edgar, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Barrington-Brown, P. R., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Bates, George, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Becker, Florence, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Beinecke, Edwin J., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Benjamin, Walter R., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Bennett Book Studios, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Berlin National Bank, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Berolzheimer, Alfred C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Beyer, Barnet J., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Bibliophile, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Biddle, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Blackburn, Philip C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Blackburn, Philip C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 11A)
  - Blackwell, B. H., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Blackwood, William & Sons, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Blanck, Jacob, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Block, Andrew, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Bodley Book Shop, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Bone, James, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Bonnell, Henry H., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Book Farm, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - The Book Shop, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Brentano's, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Brick Row Book Shop, undated; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Bright, Robert S., undated; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - British Museum, undated; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Broadbent, N. M., undated; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Brontë, undated; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Brooks, Philip, undated; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Brown, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Brown, William, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Browning, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Brussel, I. R., 1930-1931; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Brussel, I. R., 1932; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Brussel, I. R., 1933; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Brussel, I. R., 1934-1942; 9 folders (Box 52, Folder 1-9)
  - Brussel, I. R., 1943-1944; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Brussel, I. R., 1943-1944; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Bumpus, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - C (General), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Calhoun, Philo C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Campion & Co., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Carman's, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie Book Shop, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Carroll, Lewis, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - L. Carroll Catalogue, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Carter, John, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Cavanaugh, C. W., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Chao, Y. R., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Chase National Bank, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Chaucer Head Book Shop, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Cheston, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Chew, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Chiswick Book Shop, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Christ Church, Oxford, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Clark, Hartley, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Clotworthy, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Colbeck, Norman, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Colbeck, Radford & Co., Ltd, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Collectors' Bookshop, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Collins, Wilkie, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - The Colophon, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Colophon Club, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Coolidge, Miss Bertha, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Coykendall, Fred, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Craik, Mrs. D. M., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Cutler, B. D., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - D (General), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Dauber & Pine, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Davis & Orioli, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Davison, G. W., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Dawson's Book Shop, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Dean, Edward L., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Deighton, Bell & Company, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - de Krafft, William, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Delano, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - de Suzannet, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Dexter, Walter, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Dickens, Charles, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Dickens' Christmas Carols, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Dickens Fellowship, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Dickson, Miss Sarah, undated; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Disraeli, Benjamin, undated; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Dobel, undated; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Dodgson, undated; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Dolphin Book Shop, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Drake, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Dulau & Company, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Dunster, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Duschnes, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - E. P. Dutton & Company, 1923-1926; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Dutton's, Inc., 1927-1930; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Dutton's, Inc., 1931-1938; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Dutton's, Inc., 1939-1943; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - E (General), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Eckel, John C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Edgerley, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Edwards, Francis, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Eliot, George, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Engel, Gabriel, 1936-1942; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Engel, Gabriel, 1943; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Engel, Gabriel, 1944; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - English Book Dealers, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Eric, Howard, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Europe - M.L.P., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Export Book Co., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - F (General), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Fairchild, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - [no folder], undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Field, Wm. B. Osgood, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Fire at Dormy House 3/14/44, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - First Edition Bookshop, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - First Edition Club, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Fish House, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Fletcher, H. M., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Fletcher, J. K. 1924-37 and Fletcher, R., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Fletcher, J. K., 1938-1939; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Fletcher, J. K., 1940-1941; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Fletcher, J. K., 1942; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Fletcher, J. K., 1943-1944; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Forman, undated; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Foyle, undated; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Fuller, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - G (General), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Gannon, Thomas J., Inc., undated; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Gaskell, undated; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Gelber, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Gissing, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Goldsmith, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Goodspeed's Book Shop, 1927-1938; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Goodspeed's Book Shop, 1939-1944; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Grant, John, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Grosberger, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Grolier Club, 1925-1938; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Grolier Club, 1939-1944; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Gulliver, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Ha - Hn (General), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Ho (General), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Hp - Hz (General), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Haight, Gordon S., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Halewood & Son, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Hall, Norman Alexander, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Halliday, Bernard, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Hamill & Barker, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Hardy, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Hargreaves, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Harmsworth, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Harper, undated; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Harris, Frank P., undated; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Hartley, Sir Harold, undated; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Hatch, Miss Evelyn M., undated; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Hatfield, C. W., undated; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Haverford College, undated; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Hawk Mountain Sanctuary Association, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - W. Heffer & Sons, Ltd., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Heise, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Hill, Walter M., 1925-1930; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Hill, Walter M., 1931-1933; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Hill, Walter M., 1934-1935; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Hill, Walter M., 1936; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Hill, Walter M., 1937-1938; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Hill, Walter M., 1939-1943; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Hills, Mrs. Gertrude, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Himbaugh & Browne, Inc., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Historical Society of Pennsylvania, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Hodgson & Co., 1925-1938; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Hollings, Frank, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Hot Springs, Virginia (The Homestead), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Howell, Alfred C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Howes, C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Howgate, James C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Hoyt, Norris Dresser, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Hughes, Thomas, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Hunley, Maxwell, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Huntington Library, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Hyman, Leonard, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - I (General), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Illustrated Newspapers, Ltd., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Income tax, undated; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Inman, Maurice, Inc., undated; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Insurance, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Ivy Club, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - J (General), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Janvier, Meredith, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Johnson, Mr. John, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Johnston, Percy, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - K (General), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - King, Raphael, Ltd., 1929-1936; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - King, Raphael, Ltd., 1937-1942; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Kingsley, C., undated; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Kingsley and Hughes (book), undated; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Kirkland, undated; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Kittredge, B. R., undated; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - L (General), undated; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Lawson, E. M., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Lemperly, Paul, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Lever, Charles, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Library (Parrish's), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Library Co. of Philadelphia, 1933-1938; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Library Co. of Philadelphia, 1940-1941; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Library Co. of Philadelphia, 1942-1944; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Library of Congress, 1928-1939; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Library of Congress, 1940-1943; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Livingston, Flora V., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Lockwood, Thomas B., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Lowe, E. C., undated; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Lowe Bros, undated; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Lundberg, Eric, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Lytton, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Ma - Me (General), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Mf - Mz (General), undated; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - James MacDonald Company, undated; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - MacManus, M. J., undated; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - MacMillan & Co., Ltd., undated; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Madan, Falconer, 1924-1926; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Madan, Falconer, 1927-1931; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Madan, Falconer & Geoffrey, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Madigan, Thomas F., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Magee, David, undated; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Maggs Bros, 1917-1926; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Maggs Bros, 1927-1930; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Maggs Bros, 1931-1932; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Maggs Bros, 1933; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Maggs Bros, 1934-1937; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Maggs Bros, 1938-1944; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Mannados Book Shop, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Marks & Co., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Elkin Mathews, Ltd., 1922-1929; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Elkin Mathews, Ltd., 1930-1935; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 8)